http://www.menopauserx.com/about_us/privacypolicy.htm

become a fan on facebook    follow us on twitter
Menopause Survival Kit
Sign up for the MenopauseRx Menopause and Perimenopause Survival Kit to receive free educational materials and coupons for products to relieve menopause symptoms including a full sized sample of a Remifemin® black cohosh supplement.
- Order Now
MenopauseRx Internet
Privacy Statement
MENOPAUSERX, INC respects the privacy of visitors to our online
site. MENOPAUSERX, INC will only collect personally identifiable
data, such as your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail
address, when it is voluntarily submitted to us at this website.
This statement discloses the privacy practices of MENOPAUSERX,
INC. By using the MENOPAUSERX, INC website, the user agrees,
without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy
Statement. This Privacy Statement may be updated from time
to time so please check back periodically. MENOPAUSERX, INC
and/or the companies we hire and are affiliated with will
use this information to comply with your requests for information
and to better serve you. We will refer to your information
to better understand your needs and how we can improve our
products and services. We may use that information to contact
you. We are the sole owner of information you voluntarily
submit to us. We will not sell the personally identifiable
information you provide at this website to any third party
except as set forth in this Privacy Statement.
This privacy statement applies to the collection and use of
information by our company on this website, but does not apply
to the information which you may send to us by other means
or the information you provide in order to redeem another
company’s coupon.
This MENOPAUSERX, INC website also uses information in aggregate
form to track the total number of visitors to our site, the
number of visitors to each page of our site, and the domain
names of our visitors' Internet service providers. No personally
identifiable information is available in this process. Some
MENOPAUSERX, INC websites use a technology called "cookies".
A cookie is a token that a server gives to your browser when
you access a website. Cookies are capable of storing many
types of data. Cookies help provide additional functionality
to the site or to help us analyze site usage more accurately.
For instance, our server may set a cookie that keeps you from
having to enter a password more than once during a visit to
one of our sites. In all cases in which cookies are used,
the cookie will not collect personally identifiable information
except with notice to you.
This MENOPAUSERX, INC website is not intended or designed
to attract children under the age of 13. We do not collect
personally identifiable data from any person we know to be
under the age of 13 and instruct children under 13 not to
send us any information.
This site is restricted to users from the United States and
those not governed by Privacy Policies of European Union.
Users from the European Union are advised not to disclose
personal information to MENOPAUSERX, INC.
As a convenience to our visitors, MENOPAUSERX, INC's site
currently contains links to a number of sites that we believe
may offer useful information. The privacy policies and procedures
described here do not apply to those sites. We suggest contacting
those sites directly for information on their data collection
and distribution policies. Any changes to this MENOPAUSERX,
INC Internet Privacy Statement will be promptly communicated
on this page.
Your Choices:
You can always choose not to provide information, even
though it might be needed to take advantage of MENOPAUSERX,
INC offers or website features.
You can add or update certain information that you send
to us. When you update information, we usually keep a copy
of the prior version for our records.
If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from
us, please e-mail us at Unsubscribe@MenopauseRx.com
Access to Your Information
In the event that MENOPAUSERX, INC and some of our assets
are sold or transferred or used as security, the information
collected on our website may be transferred to third parties
as part of that transaction. MENOPAUSERX, INC may also provide
information or provide access to information to any of our
affiliated businesses or to our business partners.
MENOPAUSERX, INC may use contact information provided by the
user to reply to the user and send information to the user.
MENOPAUSERX, INC does not intend to reveal individually identifiable
information to third parties except in the manner stated in
the Privacy Statement. MENOPAUSERX, INC will provide aggregated
information received from users to third parties. MENOPAUSERX,
INC takes commercially reasonable precautions to prevent the
aggregated information provided to third parties from including
significant individually identifiable information.
If MENOPAUSERX, INC is requested by law enforcement officials
or judicial authorities to provide information on individual
users, MENOPAUSERX, INC may, without your consent, provide
such information. In matters involving claims of personal
or public safety, MENOPAUSERX, INC may provide a user's personal
information to appropriate authorities without your consent
or court process.
Will Your Information Be Secure?
MENOPAUSERX, INC recognizes that visitors to our websites
are concerned about the security of their personal information,
and we are committed to employing reasonable technology in
order to protect the security of our website. However, even
with the best technology, no website is 100% secure. We will
take reasonable measures which we believe are appropriate
to protect your information from loss, misuse, alteration
or destruction, and, where possible, will ask that any third
parties to whom we may transfer your information take comparable
steps to protect that security.
©Copyright 1998 - 2010 MenopauseRx.com. All rights reserved. Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Menopause Survival Kit | Menopause Products | Menopause Symptoms
and Treatments | Free
Assessment Quizzes | Site Map
Web Development and Design provided by Herrington & Company, LLC
